你知道漫画英雄世界里谁最有种吗
You know who's gonna be the bravest person in the Marvel Universe?
能给女浩克做比基尼蜜蜡除毛的最有种
Whoever has to give She-Hulk a bikini wax.
超英雄  绿巨人的表妹
要说有种嘛
You want to talk brave,
美国队长那位从墨西哥偷渡过来的园丁怎么样
how about Captain America's undocumented Mexican gardener?
超级英雄  被视为美国精神的象征
他比不上那个每次办完事后都上厕所的哥们
He's not braver than whoever uses the bathroom after The Thing?
果不其然  你们又错了
As usual, you're all wrong.
漫画英雄世界里最有种的人
The bravest person in the Marvel Universe
是那位给金刚狼做前列腺检查的医生
is the doctor who gives Wolverine his prostate exam.
那被金刚狼做前列腺检查的哥们儿呢
How about the guy who gets a prostate exam from Wolverine?
你这是抬杠吧
Now you're just being silly.
金刚狼可从来没表示过
Wolverine's never displayed
对帮助他人预防前列腺癌的
the slightest interest in helping others
有一点点兴趣
prevent prostate cancer.
喂
Hello.
对  电梯坏掉了
Yes, the elevator's out of order;
你得爬楼梯了
you'll have to use the stairs.
你当然可以
Of course you can.
披萨的历史可以追溯到16世纪
Pizza dates back to the 16th century,
可世界上第一部电梯1852年才面世
while the first elevator was not installed until 1852.
也就是说在三百多年的时间里
That means that for over 300 years,
人们都是爬楼梯送披萨的
people carried pizzas up stairs.
请继承这一光荣传统吧
Be part of that proud tradition.
趁他往披萨上吐口水的功夫  我去叫佩妮过来
I'll go get Penny while that guy spits on our food.
你觉得金刚狼是不是有个金刚不坏前列腺呢
Do you think they gave Wolverine an adamantium prostate?
这问题真傻逼
That's a stupid question.
我们不是在讨论如何检查超级英雄的菊花吗
We're having a conversation about probing the heinie of superheroes.
这有什么傻逼的
There are no stupid questions.
找谁啊
Yes?
哦  佩妮在吗
Oh, um, is Penny here?
你就是莱纳德  对吗
You're Leonard, right?
对啊
Yeah.
妈的  终于见到你了  小子
Damn, it's good to finally meet you, son.
有谁能给我补充点背景知识吗
Okay, I think a bit of context here might help.
嗨  莱纳德  你见过我爸爸了
Oh, hey, Leonard. I see you met my dad.
哇  好了
Oh, good.
背景清楚了
Context.
进来吧  伙计
Come on in, buddy.
进来坐会儿
Take a load off.
老爸  莱纳德没时间
Oh, gee, Dad, Leonard can't stay.
他只是顺道来打招呼的
He just dropped by to say hello.
谢谢你过来  亲爱的
Thanks for stopping by, sweetie.
咱俩回聊
I'll see you later.
拜
Bye.
真诡异
That was odd.
生活大爆炸第四季第九集
你确定这点儿漫画书就够了吗
Are you sure you have enough comics?
到时候你可得守12个小时的望远镜
You're going to be monitoring the telescope for 12 hours,
而据我估算你挑的这些书
and by my estimate, you've only selected
只够看7个小时的
seven hours of reading material.
我还算上了
That's even factoring in
你纠结美国漫画书里这些俚语的时间
your difficulty in parsing American comic book idioms
比如"嘭"  "唰"
like "Bamf!" and "Snikt!"
他这算种族歧视吗
Is that racist?
我觉得挺像的
It feels racist.
别太敏感了
Don't be oversensitive.
他是说你文盲  又不是说印度人都文盲
He's calling you illiterate, not your race.
哦  那就好
Oh, okay. Good.
我不用再挑漫画书了
I don't need more comics.
霍华德到时候会过来  我们会一起玩
Howard's gonna stop by, we're gonna play
星际战舰和印度大富翁
Intergalactic Battleship and Indian Monopoly.
我可不喜欢大富翁的新版本
I don't care for novelty editions of Monopoly.
我更喜欢经典的  普通版的和克林贡版的
I prefer the classics: regular and Klingon.
其实印度大富翁
Actually, Indian Monopoly's
和普通版差不多  只是钱变成了卢比
just like regular, except the money's in rupees,
酒店变成了呼叫中心而已
instead of hotels you build call centers,
如果你抽机会卡  有可能死于痢疾
and when you pick a Chance card, you might die of dysentery.
顺便告诉你
Just FYI,
这才叫种族歧视
that was racist.
你们肯定猜不到刚才发生了什么
You'll never guess what just happened.
你走在去门厅的路上
You went out in the hallway,
一不小心跌进了异次元空间之门
stumbled into an interdimensional portal
来到了5000年后的未来
which brought you 5,000 years into the future,
然后你在那里利用当时的先进技术
where you took advantage of the advanced technology
造了一架时间机器  现在你是回来
to build a time machine, and now you're back
接我们去7010年
to bring us all with you to the year 7010
那时候我们就能被派到飞海豚利用通灵术
where we are transported to work at the Thinkatorium
控制的思维水族馆工作了
by telepathically controlled flying dolphins?
错
No.
佩妮刚才吻了我
Penny kissed me.
这怎么猜得出来
Well, who would ever guess that?
是  是哪种吻啊
What-what kind of a kiss?
长吻啊  嘴对嘴的
A big kiss. On the mouth.
会不会是她本来想吻你的脸的
Is it possible that she was going for your cheek
结果你的脸一偏她就亲到嘴唇了
and you moved and she accidentally got lip?
我跟我妈经常这样
That happens with me and my mom all the time.
她跟她老爸介绍了我
She introduced me to her father,
吻完我以后就当我面把门关了
kissed me and then shut the door in my face.
也许这是暗示
Maybe she was trying to send you a message.
真的吗
You think?
是啊  暗示"这个男的不是我爸爸
Yeah. "This man is not my father.
我被挟持了
I'm being held hostage.
所以我要做一些
So I'm going to do
疯狂之举好暗示你
something insane in the hopes
去报警"
that you'll call 911."
佩妮吻我可不是什么疯狂之举
Penny kissing me is not insane.
她以前经常吻我的
She used to kiss me all the time.
爱因斯坦对精神病的定义是  "翻来覆去地
Einstein defined insanity as "Doing the same thing
重复一件事并期冀得到不同的结果"
over and over again and expecting different results."
根据这个标准
By that standard,
佩妮病得不轻
Penny is cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
我只是觉得
I'm just saying,
那个吻有些意味深长
it felt like it may have meant something.
这话让我想起从前了
Ah, this takes me back.
那时候佩妮让莱纳德如此着迷
Leonard obsessing about Penny.
别误会  我挺喜欢你现在的状态
I mean, don't get me wrong, I love your new stuff,
但偶尔听听你的痴情独白还是蛮有意思的
but once in a while it's nice to hear the hits.
你再说一遍"我们的孩子会才貌双全"
Do "Our babies will be smart and beautiful."
每次想起这句话我就笑得不行
That one always makes me laugh.
我真是吃饱了撑着跟你们聊天
Why do I bother talking to you people?
我想说其实我们根本没在听  可能你会感觉好点
If it'll make you feel better, we rarely listen.
能出来说句话吗
Hey, can I talk to you out here for a sec?
当然
Yeah, sure.
我有预感那个披萨永远也不会送来了
I'm starting to think we're never going to see that pizza.
你可能在琢磨刚才是怎么回事
So you're probably wondering what that was all about.
什么  你指你吻我那件事吗
What, uh, the kissing and everything?
没什么  经常有女人对我这样的啦
Nah, women do that to me all the time.
好吧  实际上  我貌似
Yeah, okay. The thing is, I kind of
跟我爸说我们又在一起了
told my father we got back together again.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
你是至今以来
Well, you're the first guy
第一个被他认可的人  知道吗
he's ever really approved of, you know?
你是个上过大学的科学家
You're a scientist who went to college
你脖子上没有纹身
and you don't have a neck tattoo
不是通缉犯  也没孩子
or outstanding warrants or...or a baby.
你以前都跟什么人在一起啊
What kind of guys did you used to go out with?
就是一般人呗
Just guys.
总之  他知道我们分手了以后伤心的要命
Anyway, when I told him we split up, he was heartbroken,
他总是问我  莱纳德好吗
and he kept bugging me,"How's Leonard?
你为什么就不能跟莱纳德和好呢
Why can't you get back together with Leonard?
我敢说莱纳德从来不会惹祸上身
I bet Leonard never tipped a cow over on himself."
tip a cow翻牛运动  美国农村的愚蠢运动
所以为了让他不再烦我
So to get him off my back,
我就跟他说咱俩和好了
I told him we worked things out.
是吗
Really?
咱俩是怎么和好的
How-how'd we manage that?
什么
What?
你道歉了吗
I mean, did you apologize?
还是你跑来追我了
Did you have to woo me?
少做白日梦了
Get over yourself.
我一个口哨  你就冲过来了
I whistled, you came running.
是吗  我可不这么认为
Yeah, no, I don't think so.
好吧  你干吗要跟我争这个
Okay, why are you arguing about this?
我只是想说
I'm just saying,
如果我们假装和好
if we fake got back together,
那也肯定不是这么和好的
that's totally not how it fake happened.
好吧  随便啦
Okay, whatever.
你能不能就跟我装到我爸离开为止
Will you please just play along until my dad leaves?
等一下  你真的想让我
Hold on, you actually want me
用我的演技和吻功
to deceive your father with some sort of
来瞒过你老爸吗
sham playacting and kissing?
我可是这方面的高手
'Cause I'm good with that.
佩妮  你在外面吗
Penny, you out here?
拜托  亲爱的  别当着我老爸这样啊
Come on, honey, not in front of my dad.
别担心  我看过你跟烂得多的人
Relax, I've seen you do a lot worse
干过严重得多的事呢
with a lot stupider.
看吧  他不介意
See? He doesn't mind.
莱纳德  我准备带你的女朋友
So, Leonard, I'm taking your gal out
去吃牛排  你要一起来吗
for a steak dinner; you want to join us?
爸  你真好人  但是莱纳德还要工作呢
Oh, Dad, that's nice, but Leonard has to work.
对吧  莱纳德
Right, Leonard?
没错  我要工作
Uh, I do, I have to work.
但我决定丢下工作来陪我的宝贝儿
But I'm gonna blow that off to spend the evening
和她的父亲  因为
with my sweetie and her father, 'cause, you know,
我就是这种体贴的男朋友
just the kind of boyfriend I am.
过来吧宝贝儿
Come here, you.
C-7
C-7.
错了
Miss.
怎么会错呢
How could that be a miss?
C-6中了  C-8也中了
C-6 was a hit, C-8 was a hit.
你的飞船肯定有一部分是在C-7上的
Part of your starship has to be on C-7.
除非飞船上有个洞
Not if it has a hole in the middle.
什么飞船上会有洞呀
What kind of spaceship has a hole in the middle?
罗慕伦战斗百吉饼
A Romulan Battle Bagel?
敲敲
Knock-knock.
太好了  你来了
Oh, great, you made it.
快进来
Come on in.
是我请她来的
I invited her.
望远镜在哪
So where's the telescope?
在夏威夷  但是拉杰可以在这里控制
It's in Hawaii, but Raj controls it from here.
他想观测波江座ε星云  从而证明
He's hoping to see Epsilon Eridani dim, which would be
有行星围绕它的轨道运行
evidence of a planet orbiting it.
所以我们就坐在这盯着屏幕
So we just sit and stare at the screen,
然后干等吗
waiting for something to happen?
咱俩租《恋恋笔记本》看的时候不就这样吗
I did it with you when we rented the Note Book.
没错  吉娜·罗兰兹是很漂亮
Yes, Gena Rowlands is a treasure.
你最好把那瓶酒开了
You'd better open up that bottle of wine
不然我的耳朵里就全是他的口水了
or I'm gonna end up with swimmer's ear.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我不能喝酒  我就要完成
I can't be drinking, I'm about to make
一个重大的科学发现了
an important scientific discovery here.
什么  伽利略的伟绩都是喝着酒完成的
What? Galileo did his best work while drinking wine.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
他是意大利人
Well, he was Italian.
意大利人不都这样吗
It's a reasonable assumption.
伙计  你是不是一张嘴
Dude, can you even open your mouth
就要一棒子打死一个民族呀
without spewing a cultural stereotype?
好吧  对不起  伽利略喝健怡雪碧
Oh, I-I'm sorry, Galileo drank Diet Sprite.
你是我的死党  她是我女朋友
Look, you're my best friend, she's my girlfriend;
你们应该培养感情
you should bond.
就像你跟我妈那样
You know, like you and my mom did.
你妈吓死我了
Your mom creeps the hell out of me.
是  但她不再叫你贫民窟的百万富翁了
Yes, but she's stopped calling you Slumdog Millionaire.
这点我的确很感激她
I do appreciate that.
酒来了
Here we go.
我想敬个酒
I'd like to propose a toast.
敬科学和友谊
To science and friendship.
等等  等一下
Hold on. Wait.
不  没事了  喝吧
No, it's okay, go ahead.
怎么了
What?
我今天在实验室里
Oh, I was working with
研究抗青霉素的淋病
penicillin-resistant gonorrhea in the lab today
所以我刚才在回忆我有没有洗手
and I was just trying to remember if I washed my hands.
谢谢你请我吃牛排  怀特
Thanks for the steak, Wyatt.
不用客气
My pleasure.
能跟佩妮找的会用餐巾的男朋友
It's nice to have dinner with a boyfriend of Penny's
一起吃饭是件好事
that knows how to use a napkin.
不好笑  老爸
So not funny, Dad.
我跟你介绍一下她之前的男朋友
Let me tell you about this one genius she was going out with,
那个叫多尼的家伙吧
this-this fella Donnie.
你别再提了行不行
Oh, will you please let it go?
多尼准备把农场废物
Donnie was gonna make millions turning farm waste
转变成生物燃料然后买给政府
into biofuel and selling it to the government.
很多人在干这行
A lot of people are doing that.
听到没
Oh, see?
但是多尼只是把猪粪混了点水
Yeah, but all Donnie did was mix pig poop with a little water
然后就灌进他妈的凯美瑞里
and pump it into his mom's Camry.
真不错
Yeah, that's great.
故事真好笑  说别的吧
It's a funny story. Moving on.
要是跟那个想把乒乓球啤酒游戏列入
And Donnie was a rocket scientist
奥林匹克项目的家伙比的话
compared to that boy
多尼也算是个火箭科学家了
who wanted to get beer pong into the Olympics.
他叫什么名字啊  宝贝儿
What was his name, sweetheart?
柯蒂斯  我肯定他在说笑
Curtis, and I'm pretty sure he was joking.
我也不知道
I don't know.
他还递了申请呢  我看他挺认真的
That petition looked real to me.
好吧  同志们该刹车了
Yeah, okay, I think this ends
今晚别再提起我前男友了
the ex-boyfriend portion of our evening.
我只是很高兴你终于找到了一位护花使者
Well, I'm just glad you finally found yourself a keeper.
谢谢  怀特
Thanks, Wyatt.
我是护花使者哟
I'm a keeper.
莱纳德  来吃个宵夜吧
Leonard, you want to come in for a nightcap?
天  老爸  他也很想
Oh, gee, Dad, he'd love to,
但莱纳德明天一早要工作
but Leonard has to work in the morning.
也许我能晚点去
Maybe I could go in a little late.
不不不  不行
No, no, no, you can't.
你的工作相当重要
Your career is far too important.
每个成功的男人背后  都有个唠叨的女人
Behind every great man is a nagging woman
让他没法享乐子  是吧  莱纳德
who won't let him have any fun, am I right, Leonard?
可不是嘛
Don't I know it.
晚安  孩子
Well, good night, son.
晚安  怀特
Good night, Wyatt.
晚安  亲爱的
Oh, good night, honey.
晚安
Good night.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
搞什么  又当众闪光[Frak出自《BSG》科幻版Fuck]
Oh, friggety-frak.
有完没完
Not this again.
3  4  6  过  得到两千卢比[印度货币]
Three, four, five-- pass go, get 2,000 rupees--
6  7
six, seven.
哎呀  不能走了  一头圣牛挡住了我去路
Whoops. Can't go any further. There's a sacred cow in my way.
伯纳黛特  你能不能告诉你男友
Bernadette, please tell your boyfriend
别再纠结印度圣牛的笑话了
to cool it with the cow jokes.
没用的
It won't help.
他要是找到一个笑话  就会一直讲个不停
Once he finds a joke he likes, he sticks with it.
没错
Yeah.
就比如他理发那次
Like his haircut material.
是啊  你理过发了吗
Oh, right. Did you get your hair cut?
"不  我全部理光了"
"No. I got them all cut."
现在还是真好笑呀
Which is still so funny.
你去到一家中餐馆
And when you go to a Chinese restaurant,
他每次都在幸运饼里拿到同一张纸条
he always gets the same fortune in his fortune cookie.
没错  "救命  我是个囚犯"
Right. "Help, I'm a prisoner
"被关在中国幸运饼工厂里"
in a Chinese fortune cookie factory."
好吧  你们侃我侃够了吧
Okay, I think that's enough about me.
没错  我们开始侃他老妈
He's right. Let's make fun of his mother.
霍华德  快来帮我搓脚
"Howard, come rub my feet!
我脚上的鸡眼痛死了
My corns are killing me!"
霍华德  快把我从浴缸里拉起来
"Howard, help me out of the tub!
我又卡在里面了
I'm stuck again!"
来了
Coming.
你好呀  小心肝
Hey, lovebug.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你知道前一个小时我都在做什么吗
You know what I've been doing for the last hour?
在本子上涂鸦心目中的
Mm, dreamily doodling "Mrs. Leonard Hofstadter"
"霍夫斯塔德太太"形象吗
in a notebook?
听我爸不停念叨
Listening to my father go on and on
你是个多么棒的人
about what a great guy you are.
你得承认  我的确很讨人喜欢
You got to admit, I am... I'm delightful.
你干嘛把事情搞这么复杂
Why are you making this so difficult?
哪里复杂了
It's not difficult for me.
我觉得很有趣
I'm having fun.
莱纳德
Leonard.
那你要我怎么样  是你挑起来的
What do you want me to do? You started this.
你想过去告诉他我们分手了吗
Do you want to go over and tell him we're broken up?
-不想  -那你想怎么样
- No. - Well, then, what do you want?
我不知道
I don't know.
难道你在跑过来之前
Don't you think that's something you should
不应该先想想清楚吗
have figured out before you stomped over here?
好吧  也许是
Maybe.
莱纳德  佩妮  刚好你们在
Leonard, Penny, excellent.
我想说我很高兴你们又在一起了
I'd like to say I'm very happy that you're back together,
如果我能有法子让自己显得更真诚些
and if I can figure out a way to do so
我肯定会不遗余力
and sound sincere, I will.
与此同时
In the meantime,
我要对室友协议进行一些修订
I'd like to go over some proposed changes
特别要提出关于佩妮
to the roommate agreement specifically to address
十分烦人的个人习惯
Penny's annoying personal habits.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
-什么个人习惯  -我列了个单子
- What personal habits? - I have a list.
顺便  第12条就是"我的天啊"的滥用
FYI, overuse of the phrase "Oh, my God" is number 12.
好吧  谢尔顿  你没必要这么做
Okay, Sheldon, you don't have to do this
-因为我和莱纳德不...  -吡吡吡吡吡
- because Leonard and I are not... Ba-ba-ba-ba.
你确定要把他也牵扯进来吗
Are you sure you want to include him in this?
牵扯进什么东西
Include me in what?
有什么正在策划中的阴谋?
Is there a plot afoot?
我可绝对不参与阴谋
I'll have no truck with plots.
好吧  你是对的
No, you're right.
不不  没有情节  不用卡车也不用走路
No, there's... there's no plots, no trucks, no feet.
还有什么烦人的习惯要讨论
So what other annoying habits shall we discuss?
我们不是讨论
Uh, we don't discuss anything.
莱纳德签署了室友协议
Leonard is the signatory to the roommate agreement.
所以  他对你的违规行为
As such, he bears responsibility
负有全责  并必须支付罚款
for all your infractions and must pay all fines.
-罚款  -是的
- Fines? - Yes.
如果佩妮又要继续在这过夜
If Penny's going to be spending nights here again,
你就得建立一个托管帐户
you'll need to set up an escrow account.
在这签名
Sign here.
你好丫  夏威夷
Hello, Hawaii.
我是帕萨迪纳市的库萨帕里博士
This is Dr. Koothrappali in Pasadena.
你想请你改放望远镜的位置
I'd like you to reposition the telescope, please.
斯嘉丽·约翰逊的家[著名女演员  超靓]
Scarlett Johansson's house!
开玩笑的啦  夏威夷
I'm kidding, Hawaii.
多谢啦[夏威夷语]
Mahalo.
嗷呜
Whoo!
我们开第二瓶酒
It might have been a mistake
根本就是个错误
to open that second bottle of wine.
吃一堑长一智嘛
Well, live and learn.
拉杰  你觉得你找的那个星球上
So, Raj, do you think this planet you're looking for
拥有适合生命生存的环境吗
could have an atmosphere that supports life?
也许吧
Maybe.
如果真是  我就出名了
If it did, I'd be famous.
我会成为杂志封面人物
I'd be on the cover of magazines.
那我就不用孤独一人住小公寓了
And then, instead of living alone
而是能住大豪宅
in my tiny apartment, I'd have a big mansion.
听起来真棒
That sounds great.
的确
It is.
如果你想一个人住空荡荡的房子
If you like wandering around a big, empty house
却没人爱着你
with no one to love you.
-我们会去看你  -不会的
- We'd come visit you. - No, you wouldn't.
你们会被我的财富和名声吓倒
You'd be intimidated by my wealth and fame.
我的朋友只有我那转基因的猴子管家
My only friends would be my genetically engineered monkey butler
还有我雇来的那侏儒真人象棋
and the little people I hired to be my living chess set.
他要开始变阴郁了吧
He's taking a turn to the dark side, isn't he?
再看看  他说不定能恢复的
Hold on. He could come back.
哦  这一切到底有何意义
Oh, what's the point of everything?
没戏了  他彻底醉了
Nope. He's gone.
你知道  我已经超过一年
You know it's been more than a year
没吻过姑娘了
since I've even kissed a girl?
你跟我说的在动漫展搭上的那姑娘呢
What about that hookup at Comic-Con you told me about?
醒醒吧  我在骗人
Oh, grow up. I was lying.
我一直在骗人  没人愿意吻我
I lie all the time. Nobody wants to kiss me.
可怜的小东西
Oh, you poor, poor thing.
拉杰  你得知道你这人很棒
Raj, you have to know you're a wonderful man.
很多姑娘都会愿意吻你的
There are a lot of girls out there who'll want to kiss you.
在哪呢
Where?
只要你努力找寻
You just have to look.
这下好玩了
Well, this was fun.
哦  有鱼咬钩了
Oh! I think I got a nibble.
小心点
Oh, be careful.
先放线
Give him some line.
好了  可以收线了
Okay, now reel him in.
看看这鱼
Oh, look at that baby.
咬得可真紧啊
They're really biting, huh?
对  你设定在"容易"时  鱼儿都这样
Yeah. They do that when you set it on easy.
是我的
Oh, that's me.
是我  亲爱的
Oh, hi, sweetie.
对  我很早就起床了  不想吵醒你
Yeah, I got up early and didn't want to wake you,
所以出去买咖啡了  回来的时候碰到莱纳德
so I went out for coffee and ran into Leonard on the way back.
你猜怎么着  我们现在在钓鱼
Guess what-- we're fishing.
对  就坐在他们沙发上钓着呢
Yeah. Right here on his couch.
宝贝  我爱你
Hey, baby. I love you!
是莱纳德
That's Leonard.
说他爱你
Says he loves you.
什么
What?
我明白了
I see.
这些都是瞎编的  是吗
The whole thing's bull squirt, huh?
我真是失望  再见
Well, that's very disappointing. Bye.
我一直有话想跟你说
There's been something I've been meaning to tell you.
真不敢相信  你们会这么骗我
I can't believe you would lie to me like that.
声明一下  我也是身不由己的
Just for the record, I did not want to be a part of this.
我等下再找你算账
I'll get to you in a minute.
不急
No hurry.
我的亲生女儿  觉得我不够爱她到
That my own daughter thinks I don't love her enough
不管她怎么选择我都会支持她
to support her no matter what choices she makes--
这太伤我心了
well, that hurts me deeply.
-抱歉老爸...  -让我说完
- I'm sorry, Daddy... - Let me finish.
我还以为你已今非昔比了
I thought we were past the days
不会再蒙骗我了
when you would try to pull the wool over my eyes.
说你内衣抽屉里的小袋子是香包
Telling me the baggie in your underwear drawer is potpourri?
卫生间里的验尿棒是查糖尿病的
And the pee stick in your bathroom is to check for diabetes?
对不起
You know, I'm sorry.
你长大了  我尊重你
You're a grown woman, and I respect your right
让你自己作决定
to make your own decisions,
我只要求你也同样尊重我
but all I ask is you respect me enough
要对我说实话
to be honest about them.
你说得对  从今以后我一定对你说实话
You're right. Look, from now on, I will tell you the truth.
谢谢  现在进去换件衣服
Thank you. Now, why don't you go and put some clothes on
趁我出发去机场前  先去吃点东西
and we'll grab a bite to eat before I head for the airport.
-而你...  -老爸  他跟着没关系...
- Now you... - Daddy, he had nothing to do...
-走你的  -好吧
- Keep walking.  - Okay.
求求你  拜托你别放弃追她
Please, please, please don't give up on her.
什么
What?
我不想再面对什么滑板白痴  白人说唱歌手
I can't go back to the skateboard idiots, the white rappers
还有那些反戴帽子满身汗臭的蠢驴们
and all those sweaty dumb-asses with their backwards hats.
天  我不知道我是否还有机会
Gee, I don't know if it's in the cards, sir.
那就作弊
Then, stack the deck.
欺骗  撒谎  我无所谓
Cheat. Lie. I don't care.
我死前还想抱上外孙
I want grandkids before I die,
而且不想他们在活动房里长大
and I want them to grow up in a house without wheels.
-那我试试  -谢谢
- I'll give it a shot.  - Thank you.
现在我来做点事帮帮你
Now I'm going to do something here to help you along.
-什么  -别怕就对了
- Excuse me?  - Just don't panic.
你这个骗人的混蛋快给我滚蛋
Now, get your sorry, lying ass out of my face
别让我再看到你
and make sure I never see it again!
逆反心理  我懂的  真聪明
Oh, the reverse psychology thing. I see. That's very clever.
别说出来  快出去
Don't yap. Just get out.
我回去上Facebook加你好友
I'll friend you on Facebook.
你来了
Oh, there you are.
跟你说  我一晚没睡
Just so you know, I was up all night,
终于完成了
but I have finally completed
针对佩妮部分的新室友协议
the Penny-specific section of the new roommate agreement.
不必了  我们又分手了
Yeah well, not necessary. We broke up again.
你有没有为别人着想过  莱纳德
Do you even think about other people, Leonard?
你想过没有
Do you?
昨晚怎么样
Oh, how'd it go last night?
你知道的
Oh, you know.
都一样的  没啥变化
Same old, same old.
通过望远镜看到些星星  就是大惊喜了
Looked through a telescope, saw some stars. Big whoop.
真的吗
Really?
这望远镜你可等了几个月了  怎么了
You waited months for time with that telescope. What happened?
干嘛  采访我写书吗
Why? You writing a book?
我提出个假设
I'm going to propose a hypothesis.
昨晚  拉杰偶然与外星文明联络上了
Last night, Raj accidentally made contact with an alien civilization
然后被美国政府要求严格保密
and has been ordered by the United States government to keep it a secret.
啥事都没有  能换个话题吗
Nothing happened. Can we please just change the subject?
这话一听就是排演过的  我们不是唯一智慧生命
That sounds rehearsed. We are not alone.
昨晚你顺利把玩上拉杰的大望远镜了吗
You get to play with Raj's big telescope last night?
这话从何说起
Where did that come from?
他从未碰过我的望远镜
He never touched my telescope.
你给我闭嘴
Way to go shutting up.
我闭嘴了  你也给我闭嘴
I did shut up. Now you shut up.
-好吧  -谢谢
- Fine.  - Thank you.
真不敢相信  你今早没给我打电话
I can't believe you didn't call me this morning.